<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sonja Hertzing&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://sonjahertzing.com/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sonja Hertzing&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 15:34:34 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://sonjahertzing.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>happy new year</title>
      <link>http://sonjahertzing.com/post/happy-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 15:34:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sonjahertzing.com/post/happy-new-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Widow&#39;s Chronicle Day 53</title>
      <link>http://sonjahertzing.com/post/widows_chronicle_day_53/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 17:33:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sonjahertzing.com/post/widows_chronicle_day_53/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am reluctant to count the days since his death. Today I did. 53. Fifty-three days since we said goodbye forever. That morning I took a little sponge and dipped it in coffee and touched it to his lips. Coffee and Bible devotion in the mornings was our custom. In my confusion I read the devotional for the day &lt;em&gt;after&lt;/em&gt; his death. God in His kindness ordained it so: Isaiah 46:4 I will be your God throughout your lifetime–until your hair is white with age. I made you, and I will care for you. That afternoon my husband was in the presence of the Author.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They tell me the hurt never goes away. It can be triggered by something so simple like the smell of his windbreaker, the sight of his watch and wedding ring on his nightstand, a melody we cherished. Sometimes the longing [read sobbing] comes at the most inopportune time: like driving in traffic. Pull over safely. “Lord, this hurts. Please take me through this.” And He does, for the moment. As humans we are destined to endure such hurts and more. But God–my favorite words in Scripture–is my Strong Tower. I will be your God throughout your lifetime…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Widow Training</title>
      <link>http://sonjahertzing.com/post/widow_training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 17:26:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sonjahertzing.com/post/widow_training/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He’s gone. It’s not that I didn’t know that he was dying, I just never wanted to accept the reality that I would be without my husband. Reality or not, he died and I am left to deal with countless emotions, situations, and decisions that demand my sole attention, for now I have no spouse to take up the slack of our everyday life. So how does a girl go about learning to be a widow? Learn-as-you-go-training, is it? A position uniquely tailored in that the husband must die in order for you to acquire the title. My heart wants to shout, Not fair!! but my head acknowledges that by all accounts we were dealt a fair amount of time together and most of it was good and wonderful and…ordinary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Were it not for my faith in God and His loving kindness to me, the loss of my husband would be unbearable. I am comforted as always by Scripture delivered characteristically at just the right time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isaiah 54:5 For thy Maker is thine Husband; the Lord of Hosts is His name; and thy Redeemer the Holy One of Israel; the God of the whole earth shall He be called.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God steps in. His care for me is on display. I submit to Him to teach me this widow role that’s been dealt to me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>