<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post-rsses on Sonja Hertzing&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://sonjahertzing.com/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post-rsses on Sonja Hertzing&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:26:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://sonjahertzing.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>widow_training</title>
      <link>http://sonjahertzing.com/post/widow_training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:26:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sonjahertzing.com/post/widow_training/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He’s gone. It’s not that I didn’t know that he was dying, I just never wanted to accept the reality that I would be without my husband. Reality or not, he died and I am left to deal with countless emotions, situations, and decisions that demand my sole attention, for now I have no spouse to take up the slack of our everyday life. So how does a girl go about learning to be a widow? Learn-as-you-go-training, is it? A position uniquely tailored in that the husband must die in order for you to acquire the title. My heart wants to shout, Not fair!! but my head acknowledges that by all accounts we were dealt a fair amount of time together and most of it was good and wonderful and…ordinary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Were it not for my faith in God and His loving kindness to me, the loss of my husband would be unbearable. I am comforted as always by Scripture delivered characteristically at just the right time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Isaiah 54:5 For thy Maker is thine Husband; the Lord of Hosts is His name; and thy Redeemer the Holy One of Israel; the God of the whole earth shall He be called.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God steps in. His care for me is on display. I submit to Him to teach me this widow role that’s been dealt to me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>